Guide to the Joe Negri Collection, 1930-2014 CAM.JNC.2014
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Original Compositions, I.
  - Poetry Forums, 7.
    - Sam Hazo International Poetry Forum: "Traveling without a Ticket"
      - "Then Break[?] Celebration" (Box 11, Folder 979-990, Item 982)
      - "The Ans. is Yes" (Box 11, Folder 979-990, Item 983)
      - "Road Song" (Box 11, Folder 979-990, Item 984)
        Photocopy of holograph score.
      - "Seascape" (Box 11, Folder 979-990, Item 985)
      - "Gentle Rain" Bass (Box 11, Folder 979-990, Item 986)
      - "Walk Soft" (Box 11, Folder 979-990, Item 987)
        photocopy of holograph manuscript by Jim Hall.
      - "Spain" (Box 11, Folder 979-990, Item 988)
        photocopy of holograph manuscript. Originally by Chick Corea.
      - "Seascape", 1982 (Box 11, Folder 979-990, Item 989)
        photocopy of holograph manuscript by Eric Kloss.
      - "On the Metroliner I Remember That to Be Is to Remember" (Box 11, Folder 979-990, Item 990)
        Photocopy of poem. 2 pages.
  - Commissioned Compositions, 8.
    - "Salute to CLO" piano lead (Box 3, Folder 160, Item 160)
      Holograph score. 3 pages. 1 copy.
    - Salute to C.L.O. piano accomp. (Box 3, Folder 160, Item 160.1)
    - Salute to CLO vocal lead (Box 3, Folder 160, Item 160.2)
    - Salute to CLO (Box 3, Folder 160, Item 160.3)
    - Intro to Salute to CLO (Box 3, Folder 160, Item 160.4)
    - Salute to CLO piano lead (Box 3, Folder 165, Item 165)
    - Letter from Joe Negri to Bernice Cohen, June 13, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 166, Item 166)
      Photocopy of typed letter on Joe's stationary presenting his "Tribute to CLO" for consideration for an award at ASCAP. 1 page.
    - Press Release from CLO, February 8, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 166, Item 166.1)
      Photocopy of press release announcing the CLO musical theme contest. 2 pages.
    - "Salute to C.L.O." (Box 3, Folder 166, Item 166.2)
    - "Civic Light Opera" (Box 3, Folder 166, Item 167.2)
      Newsclipping from the Pittsburgh Courier announcing Joe winning the CLO Musical Theme Contest.
    - Guitarist-Composer (Box 3, Folder 166, Item 167.1)
      Photocopy of newsclipping from the Pittsburgh Press announcing that Joe won the CLO's musical theme contest.
    - "Triangle Tattler: 'Loverly' Theme for CLO" (Box 3, Folder 166, Item 167.3)
      Photocopy of article by George Anderson from the Pittsburgh Post-gazette announcing Joe winning the CLO Musical Theme contest.
    - Three newsclippings about Joe winning the CLO musical theme contest (Box 3, Folder 166, Item 167.4)
      Photocopy of three newsclippings on one page.
    - Letter from Joe Negri to Dorothy Jetter, June 11, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 167, Item 167)
      Photocopy of letter on Joe's letter head to ASCAp regarding his "Tribute to CLO."
    - "Salute to CLO" (Main Theme for Pittsburgh Civic Light Opera), March 20, 1980 (Box 28, Reel 1879)
      1 reel
      Original Inscription: C.L.O. - Theme Music Orig: Joe Negri Written March 1980 Recorded march 20, 1980 Bill Chrystal - Piano I Joe Negri - Piano II
    - Women of Spirit usage agreement, August 17, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3-4.2, Item 3)
      Photocopy of agreement between Joe Negri and Carlow College for use of "Woman of Spirit."
      Contents originally enclosed in green folder with the following inscription:
      Carlow College (Women of Spirit) 1995
    - "Woman of Spirit", June, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3-4.2, Item 4)
      Photocopy of holograph score. 4 pages.
    - "Woman of Spirit" music under narration, June 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3-4.2, Item 4.1)
      Photocopy of holograph score. 2 pages. 2 copies.
    - Motifs - Ideas (Box 1, Folder 3-4.2, Item 4.2)
      Holograph score. 1 page.
    - "Woman of Spirit", June 1995 (Box 3, Folder 154, Item 154)
      Carlow College Woman of Spirit Song Original Copy Joe Negri/Josie Carey
    - "Woman of Spirit" music under narration, June 1995 (Box 3, Folder 154, Item 154.1)
    - "Woman of Spirit" (Carlow College) (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - John Reed King Show, 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 1931-1938, Item 1932)
    - Wirebound manuscript book of holograph manuscripts for the John Reed King Show (Box 1929, Folder 1931-1938, Item 1931)
      Belwin Wire bound manuscript book. Contains the following holograph scores:
      Man at Large Theme Fan-Fares Thru the Years Long Last Love Put on a Happy Face I've Got My Love to Keep Me Warm Heart Stood Still Hey there Let it Snow Gone with the Wind Bidin' My time Greensleaves Irish Melody You Do Something to Me Witchcraft Wild About Harry Theme St. Louis Medley Mi Bist de Shane 2 Brothers Dick Van Dyke Danny thomas Instant I.Q.
    - God, the Earth, and Man (Box 1929, Folder 1931-1938, Item 1932)
      Typed lyrics. 2 pages. Lyrics by Robert J. McCully; Music by Joe Negri
      Originally found interleavened in item 1931.
    - This is all I ask (Box 1929, Folder 1931-1938, Item 1933)
    - Happy Face (medley) (Box 1929, Folder 1931-1938, Item 1934)
    - Recognize the Tune (Box 1929, Folder 1931-1938, Item 1935)
      Holograph manuscript. 1 pages.
    - Camelot (Box 1929, Folder 1931-1938, Item 1936)
    - If Ever I Would Leave You (Box 1929, Folder 1931-1938, Item 1937)
    - Folk Material (Box 1929, Folder 1931-1938, Item 1938)
      handwritten list of songs on notepaper.
  - Mass of Hope
    - Mass of Hope Program, May 21, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 1941-1943, Item 1941)
      Program for Joe Negri's "Mass of Hope" at St. John the Baptist Catholic Church. 2 copies.
    - "Mass of Hope" Chronicle (Box 28, Folder 1941-1943, Item 1942)
      Typed notes about the process of putting the Mass of Hope together.
    - East Liberty Presbyterian Church program, May 9, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 1941-1943, Item 1943)
      Program for service using portions of Joe Negri's "Mass of Hope."
  - McKeesport Symphony Orchestra
    - Program McKeesport Symphony Orchestra, March 9, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 257, Item 257)
      Program for Negri performance of Gershwin medley, Flight of the Bumblebee, On a Wonderful Day, and You Are Special with the McKeesport Symphony Orchestra.
  - Stephen Foster Commemoration Events
    - "Dolly Day" (Box 28, Folder 1945, Item 1945)
      Typed lyrics for Joe Negri's version of Stephen Foster's "Dolly Day."
    - "Gentle Annie and Laura Lee", February 15, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 1945.1, Item 1945.1)
- Published Sheet Music, II.
  Commercially published sheet music written by other composers (NOT Joe Negri).
  - "Lucy to Be Me" (Box 25, Item 1401)
    Music by Leonard Bernstein; Lyrics by Betty Comden & Adolph Green New York: M. Witmark & Sons, 1964
  - "Send in the Clowns" (Box 25, Item 1402)
    Music and lyrics by Stephen Sondheim New York: Revelation Music Publishing Group, 1973
  - "I Remember It Well" (Box 25, Item 1403)
    Lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner; Music by Frederick Loewe New York: Chappell & Co, Inc., 1957
  - "Chim Chim Cher-ee" (Box 25, Item 1404)
    Printed score By Richard M. Shermand and Robert B. Sherman Wonderland Music Co., 1963
  - "Bewitched" (Box 25, Item 1405)
    Words and music by Howard Greenfield and Jack Keller Screen Gems, Columbia Music, Inc., 1964
  - "Theme from "Star Trek"" (Box 25, Item 1406)
    Words by Gene Roddenberry, music by Alexander Courage G&W Bruin Music Company, 1970
  - Dueling Banjos
    - "Dueling Banjos" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1409)
      Based on "Feudin' Banjos" written by Arthur Smith New York: Warner Bros., 1973
    - "Dueling Banjos" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1409.1)
      Photocopy of published score from 1409.
    - "Dueling Banjos" for guitar (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1409.2)
    - [Untitled script] (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1409.3)
      script for Tiny Tots Concert with the Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra. Typed. Four pages.
  - "When I Look in Your Eyes" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1412)
    Words and Music by Leslie Bricusse. New York: Hastings Music Corporation, 1967
  - "Talk to the Animals" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1413)
    Words and music by Leslie Bricusse. New York: Hastings Music Corporation, 1967.
  - "I Think I Like You" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1414)
    Words and music by Leslie Bricusse. NY: Hastings Music Corporation, 1967.
  - "After Today" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1415)
    Words and music by Leslie Bricusse NY: Hastings Music Corporation, 1967
  - "Now That We're in Love" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1416)
    Music by George Barrie, Lyric by Sammy Cahn New York: Brut Music Publishing Co., 1975
  - "Love is a Ball" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1417)
    Words by Richard Adler; Music by Michel Legrand
    New York: United Artists Music Co., 1963.
    Handwritten notation of guitar chords in score.
  - "Teamwork" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1418)
    Words by Sammy Cahn; Music by James Van Heusen New York: Chappell & Co., Inc., 1962
  - "The Eyes of Love" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1419)
    Music by Quincy Jones; Lyric by Bob Russell NY: Shamley Music Corporation, 1967
  - "Baby the Rain Must Fall" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1420)
    Photocopy of published score. 2 copies.
    Words and music by Elmer Bernstein and Ernie Sheldon.
  - "A Thousand Clowns" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1421)
    Words and music by Gerry Mulligan and Judy Holiday. NY: United Artists Music Co., 1963
  - "That's Entertainment" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1422)
    2 copies Words by Howard Dietz; music by Arthur Schwartz NY: Chappell & Co, 1953
  - "That's Entertainment" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1422A)
    handwritten lyrics on notebook paper to "That's Entertainment" by Arthur Schwartz and Howard Dietz.
  - "That's Entertainment" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1422B)
    Photocopy of published score of "That's Entertainment" with handwritten changes.
  - "The Summer Knows" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1423)
    Lyric by Marilyn and Alan Bergman; Music by Michel Legrand. NY: Warner Bros Music, 1971
  - "Theme from Love Story" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1424)
    Music by Francis Lai NY: Famous Music Corp, 1970
  - "You Light Up My Life" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1425)
    words and music by Joe Brooks. Big Hill Music Corp, 1977 photocopy of printed score. 3 pages.
  - "Main Title" (from Star Wars) (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1426)
    music by John Williams Fox Fanfare Music 1977
  - "Ca, C'est L'Amour" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1427)
    Words and music by Cole Porter. NY: Buxton Hill Music Corp, 1957
  - "Money Burns a Hole in My Pocket" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1428)
    Words by Bob Hilliard; Music by Jule Styne. NY: Chappell & Co., 1954
  - "The Long Hot Summer" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1429)
    Lyric by Sammy Cahn; music by Alex North NY: Leo Feist Inc., 1958
  - "Small Talk" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1430)
    Words and music by Richard Adler and Jerry Ross. NY: Frank Music Corp, 1954
  - "Grease" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1431)
    Words and music by Barry Gibb NY: Warner Bros, 1978
  - "Grease" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1431.1)
    Photocopy of printed score from 1430. 2 copies.
  - "A Man and a Woman" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1433)
    English words by Jerry Keller; Music by Francis Lai Northern Music Corporation, 1966
  - "The Windmills of Your Mind" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1434)
    Lyric by Marilyn and Alan Bergman; Music by Michel Legrand NY: United Artists Music Co. Inc., 1968
  - "Breakfast at Tiffany's" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1435)
    music and lyrics by Henry Mancini. Famous Music Corporation, 1961 handwritten notes on cover.
  - "Days of Wine and Roses" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1436)
    Music by Henry Mancini; Words by Johnny Mercer NY: M. Witmark & Sons, 1962.
  - "I Like to Lead When I Dance" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1437)
    Words by Sammy Cahn; Music by James van Heusen NY: Criterion Music Corp., 1964
  - "Theme from Lawrence of Arabia" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1438)
    music by Maurice Jarre NY: Gower Music, Inc, 1962
  - "Mr. Hobbs Theme" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1439)
    Music by Henry Mancini NY: Miller Music Corp, 1962
  - "The Green Leaves of Summer" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1440)
    Lyric by Paul Francis Webster; Music by Dimitri Tiomkin NY: Leo Feist Inc., 1960
  - "The Second Time Around" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1441)
    Words by Sammy Cahn; Music by James van Heusen Miller Music Corporation, 1960
  - "No Two People" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1442)
    Music by Frank Loesser Ny: Frank Music Corp, 1951
  - "Something's Coming" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1443)
    from West Side Story. Music by Leonard Bernstein; words by Stephen Sondheim. NY: G. Schirmer, INc., 1962.
  - "The Second Time Around" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1444)
    words by Sammy Cahn; music by James van Heusen NY: Miller Music Corp, 1960
  - "Suddenly It's Spring" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1445)
    Words by Johnny Burke, music by Jimmy van Heusen Famous Music Corporation, 1943
  - "The Key to Love" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1446)
    Words by John Moran, music by Charles Williams NY: Mills Music, 1960
  - "Theme from Valley of the Dolls" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1447)
    Lyrics by Dory Previn, Music by Andre Previn NY: Leo Feist, Inc., 1967
  - "The Look of Love" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1448)
    From Casino Royale. Music by Burt Bacharach; lyrics by Hal David NY: Colgems Music, 1967
  - "Watch What Happens" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1449)
    from The Umbrellas of Cherbourg. Lyrics by Norman Gimbel; Music by Michel Le Grand. NY: Cimino Publications, 1967
  - "You're Gonna Hear from Me" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1450)
    Music by Andre Previn; Words by Dory Previn. NY: Remick Music Corp, 1965
  - "If I Were a Bell" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1451)
    From Guys and Dolls by Frank Loesser. NY: Frank Distributing Corp, 1950
  - "Guys and Dolls" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1451A)
    from Guys and Dollss by Frank Loesser. NY: Frank Music Corp, 1950
  - "Sue Me" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1452)
  - "Fugue for Tinhorns" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1453)
  - "Sit Down You're Rockin' the Boat" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1454)
  - "Selection from Carousel" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1456)
    From Carousel. Words by Oscar Hammerstein 2nd; Music by Richard Rodgers. NY: T.B. Harms, 1945
  - "Selection from Kiss Me Kate" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1457)
    Music and Lyrics by Cole Porter. NY: T.B. Harms Co., 1949
    Handwritten notes throughout.
  - "No Strings" Vocal Selection (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1458)
    Words and music by Richard Rodgers. NY: Williamson Music Inc., 1962
  - "Piano Selection from Fanny" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1459)
    Music and lyrics by Harold Rome.
    NY: Chappell & Co., Inc., 1955
  - "Piano Selection from Flower Drum Song" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1460)
    Music by Richard Rodgers; lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein 2nd.
    NY: Williamson Music, 1959
  - "Selection from The King and I" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1461)
    Words by Oscar Hammerstein 2nd; Music by Richard Rodgers NY: Williamson Music Inc., 1951
  - "They're Playing My Song" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1467)
    Music by Marvin Hamlisch; Lyrics by Carole Bayer Sager.
    NY: Chappell & Co., 1979
  - "Romeo & Juliet Souvenir Music Album" (Box 25, Folder 1409, Item 1468)
    Music by Nino Rota. NY: Famous Music Corporation, 1969
- Songbooks, III.
  Commercially published songbooks by other composers (NOT Joe Negri).
  - "Cole Porter Portfolio: A Vocal Album of Eleven Songs" (Box 26, Item 1252)
    NY: Buxton Hill Music Corp, 1954.
  - "Vocal Selections from "Mame"" (Box 26, Item 1253)
    Music and Lyrics by Jerry Herman NY: Edwin H. Morris & Co., 1966
  - Peak of the Pops (Box 26, Item 1395)
    Miami, Florida: Screen Gems, 1974 The Air that I Breathe Another Saturday Night come and Get Your Love Dancing Machine The Entertainer for the Love of Money Hooked on a Feeling If You Love Me (Let me Know) I'm Leaving it (All) up to you (I've Got to Use my) Imagination Jazzman (The) Joker Just Don't Want to be Lonely Let Me Be There Living for the City (The) Loco-Motion Lookin' for a Love (to Call My Own) (The) Lord's Prayer (The) Most Beautiful Girl My Melody of Love Nothing from Nothing Oh MY My Oh Ver Young Piano Man Rock On show and Tell Stop and Smell the Roses (The) Streak Tell me Something Good Then Came You TSOP Tubular bells Until You Come Back to Me (That's What I'm Gonna Do) (The) Way We Were You and Me Against the World You make me Feel Brand New
  - "Somewhere in the Night: And 26 Other Greatest Hits" (Box 26, Item 1396)
    Almo Publications, 1970
    Somewhere in the Night I go to Rio Sing for the Day A Little More Love Soul Man September I Will Survive Shake Your Groove Thing I Just Wanna Stop A Little Lovin' I Believe You Last Dance Hold Me, Touch Me (Think of Me When We're Apart) Radioactive Don't Cry Out Loud Got to Have Lovin' One Last Kiss Cuz It's You, Girl Ain't that Enough for You I Love New York Bouree Baby Hold On Short People Blue Collar Man (Long Nights) Looks Like We Made It Fantasy Belle
  - "The Wiz Vocal Selections" (Box 26, Item 1397)
    Music and Lyrics by Charlie Smalls The Wiz Company, 1974
  - "Tell It Like It Is: A Folk Muiscal for Choir and Solos" (Box 26, Item 1398)
    Composed by Ralph Carmichael and Kurt Kaiser Waco, TX: Lexicon Music, Inc, 1969.
  - "Professional Guide of Popular Standard Songs Folio One" (Box 26, Item 1399)
    NY: Mills Music, Inc.,
  - "Familiar song Hits by Jimmy McHugh" (Box 26, Item 1400)
    NY: Robbins Music Corp, 1960.
  - "Braggarty Rabbit from Tales of Rhyme and Reason" (Box 26, Item 1455)
    By Seymour Barab NY: Boosey & Hawkes, 1970
  - "Vocal Selections from Kismet" (Box 26, Item 1462)
    Music and Lyrics by Robert Wright and George Forrest NY: Frank Music Corp, 1953
  - "Vocal Selection from Woman of the Year" (Box 26, Item 1464)
    Music by John Kander; Lyrics by Fred Ebb. NY: Fiddleback Music Publishing Co, 1981
  - "Vocal Selections from Guys and Dolls" (Box 26, Item 1465)
    Music and Lyrics by Frank Loesser. NY: Frank Music Corp., 1955
  - "Vocal Selections from "How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying" (Box 26, Item 1466)
    Music and lyrics by Frank Loesser.
    NY: Frank Music Corp, 1961
  - "Vocal Selections from The Roar of the Greasepaint - The Smell of the Crowd" (Box 26, Item 1469)
    By Leslie Bricusse and Anthony Newley.
    The Richmond Organization, 1965
  - "Vocal Selection from Pippin" (Box 26, Item 1471)
    Written by Stephen Schwartz. NY: Belwin Mills, 1972
  - "Songs in the Key of Life" (Box 26, Item 1386)
    by Stevie wonder. Columbia Pictures Publications, 1976
  - "Songs in the Key of Life" (Box 26, Item 1386.1)
    Songs by Stevie Wonder. LP Insert with lyrics.
  - "The Paul Simon Song Book The Best of Simon & Garfunkel" (Box 26, Item 1387)
    Songs by Paul Simon and Art Garfunkey. NY: Charing Cross Music, 1966
  - "Songs by Paul Simon" (Box 26, Item 1388)
    NY: Charing Cross Music, 1967
  - "Jarreau" (Box 26, Item 1390)
    songs by Al Jarreau. NY: Warner Brothers Records, 1983
  - "The Music of Jimmy Webb" (Box 26, Item 1391)
    Charles Hansen Publications, 1967
  - "Carole King Music" (Box 26, Item 1392)
    Miami, Fl: Columbia Publications, 1971
  - "The Third Golden Beatles Album" (Box 26, Item 1393)
    Hansen Publications, Inc. 1967. Cartoon of Beatles pasted on cover of book.
  - "Stevie Wonder Gold" (Box 26, Item 1394)
    Arranged for Easy piano by Richard Bradley.
    Jobete Music Company, Inc., 1975
- Recordings, IV.
  Recordings divided into two categories: those by Joe Negri (both commercial and non) and those by others (both commercial and non).
  - Joe Negri Recordings, 1.
    - "Bluesville" (Box 27, Record 1905)
      45 rpm disc. Audio disc.
    - "Caprice Vienouse Singing Strings" (Box 27, Record 1895)
      KDKA on-air recording on Audiodisc.
    - Christmas Music (Box 28, Reel 1880)
      1 Reel to Reel
      Original Inscription Christmas Is (Long Version Instr) Christmas Is (Short version Instr) - Standard not original Christmas Waltz Happy Long Ago - Original Holidays & Children - (2:40) Original Marvelous Toy -Pause- Pretty Girl (Pgh Show) 71/2 IPS Full Track
    - WTAE Christmas Show (Box 28, Reel 1883)
      1 reel. Original Inscription: J. Negri - WTAE Xmas Show 1964 1883.1 Inside Container
    - "Arthur Godfrey Talent Scouts Show" (Box 28, Reel 1882)
      Original inscription: Arthur Godfrey Talent Scouts Show
    - "Summer Sounds" (Box 28, Reel 1881)
      Original Inscription. Summer Sounds - (July 66) Sound track -
    - WTAE Easter Seals Music (Box 28, Reel 1884)
      Original Inscription.
      Film Title - "The Boy Who was Half Past Three" Produced for the Easter Seals Society by (WTAE-TV) Music Composed by Joe Negri - Arranged by Kloman Schmit Classical Guitar Joe Negri Cello Allan Sher* Flute & Piccolo Ethan Stang*
      Main Title Theme - Sub Title Theme - (Minor mode Em) Waltz Theme -
      *Mr. Stang & Mr. Sher were members of the Pgh Symphony
    - [Untitled Reel to Reel for WTAE-TV] (Box 28, Reel 1744)
      1 reel Original inscription Cut 1-30 sec. Cut 2 2-60 sec. Ch. 4 Hello Pgh
    - "Flying Home" (Box 27, Record 1904)
      Recording on Wilcox-Gay Recordio disc.
    - "The Girl Next Door" (Box 27, Record 1908)
    - "Guitar with Love" (Box 27, Record 1907)
      Commercially released album Containing:
      Side 1 1. Lazy Day 2. The Boy (Girl) Next Door 3. spring in Manhattan 4. Harlequin 5. Django 6. A Felicidade
      Side 2 1. The Tiny Whistle 2. A Time for Love 3. Serenata 4. 'Round Midnight 5. Watch What Happens 6. After Today
    - "Hamps Boggie/If I Had You", September 21, 1945 (Box 27, Record 1899)
      45 rpm disc on "Presto" brand record.
    - "How High the Moon" (Box 27, Record 1892)
      Recorded by Joe Negro Trio. Audio Disc recording. Reverse side has:
      Pennies from Heaven marvelous for Words Penthouse Serenade
    - "Jazz Quintet" (Box 27, Record 1891)
      Wayne Recording company disc. 33 1/3.
      Side one: All God's Children Got Rhythm Autumn Leaves Flight of the Bumble Bee
      Side two: Cherokee Jolly-Joe
    - "Joe Negri Trio" (Box 27, Record 1889)
      Audiodisc blank record. Both sides marked Joe Negri Trio, early '50s.
    - "Lisa" (Box 27, Record 1903)
      Audio disc blank record. 2nd side marked "stage fright".
    - "Ma Leguena" (Box 27, Record 1890)
      KQV Air check on Soundcraft 33 1/3 disc.
    - "Minute Waltz", October 21, 1948 (Box 27, Record 1901)
      War Recording Service.
      Guitarist Joe Negri KDKA "Singing Strings" Program, Aircheck.
    - "Porto Bay" (Box 27, Record 1896)
      Joe Negri Trio on 45 rpm Audiodisc blank recording.
    - "Sunny Side of Street", September 21, 1945 (Box 27, Record 1900)
      Duodisc recording, 78 rpm. Joe & Bob Negri.
    - "They'll Never Be Another You/Summertime" (Box 27, Record 1893)
      Fremont 1-7800 Audio-Video Company, Wilkinsburg. 78 rpm disc.
    - "This is No Ordinary Girl" (Box 27, Record 1897)
      Telaword Records, 78 rpm disc. Recorded by Lennie Martin at Carlton House, Pittsburgh.
    - "Tico, Tico/ Nancy with the Laughing Face", September 21, 1945 (Box 27, Record 1898)
      Performance by Joe and his brother Bob on September 21, 1945. Presto record.
    - "Trimacki in Concert", 1940s (Box 27, Item 1894)
      Joe Negri Trio. Audiodisc recording disc.
    - "Woman of Stone" (Box 27, Record 1888)
      Also includes "I Like the Girls." Music by Joe Negri, Lyrics by Bob McCully from Beck's Summer Shows. 33 rpm disc.
    - "Yesterdays" (Box 27, Record 1902)
      Guitar solo by Joe Negri. Audio disc recording blank. 2nd Side "Stagefright" solo by Joe Negri.
    - "The Girl Next Door" (Box 27, Record 1908)
      Bell Sound Stereo, New York. 33 1/3.
      Side I:
      1. The Girl Next Door 2. Spring in Manhattan 3. Lazy Day 4. Harlequin 5. Django 6. Felicidad
      Side 2: 1. After Today 2. A Time for Love 3. Tin-Whistle 4. Round About Midnight 5. Watch What Happens 6. Serenata